ozcarguide.com 2008-09-19

# Privacy Policy and Disclaimer - Australia Car Guide

## BASIC CONFIDENTIALITY & PRIVACY POLICY

OzCarGuide.com hereafter OzCarGuide, considers personal information, such as your name, postal and e-mail addresses or telephone number, to be private and confidential. Accordingly, the personal information you provide is stored in a secure location, is accessible only by designated staff or authorized agents, and is used only to market our products or better serve our customers. OzCarGuide will not disclose any personal information to other organizations.

## INFORMATION COLLECTION

When you browse a OzCarGuide web site, you do so anonymously. Personal information is not collected. Some areas of our web sites, however, may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, including your name, email address, etc., for purposes such as correspondence, site registration, making a purchase, or participating in online surveys.

OzCarGuide may also retain electronic communications you send to our customer service representatives, webmaster or other associates. These may be shared only within OzCarGuide as a means to continually improve customer service.

OzCarGuide web sites track information about the visits to those sites. For example, statistics are compiled that show the daily number of visitors to a site, the daily requests received for particular files on a site, and what countries those requests come from. These aggregated statistics are used to customize our web site to better meet your needs and may also be provided to others, but the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.

There is a technology called "cookies" which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a web site. A cookie is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. Certain OzCarGuide sites may use cookies so that we can better serve site users. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.

## INFORMATION USE

Personal information that visitors submit to our sites is used only for the purpose for which it is submitted unless we disclose other uses in this Internet Privacy Policy or at the time of collection. Copies of correspondence sent from the web site, that may contain personal information, are stored as archives for record-keeping and back up purposes only. You should be aware that providing information to any of our subscribing businesses through our site will result in the information being passed to that business and your information will then be held subject to the privacy obligations of that business which may not conform with this Privacy Policy.

## DISCLOSURE INFORMATION

Because OzCarGuide considers the individual information we maintain to be confidential, our policy is to disclose no personal information gathered on-line to third parties unless release is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or government investigations or proceedings. OzCarGuide does not sell, rent or transmit personal information to other organisations.

## OTHER WEBSITES

OzCarGuide may contain links to other sites, and we make every effort to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy. However, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites.

## CHILDREN

OzCarGuide has no intention of collecting any personally identifiable information (such as name, address, or telephone number) from individuals under sixteen years of age. Where appropriate, OzCarGuide will specifically instruct children not to submit such information on our web site.

## DISCLAIMER

By using OzCarGuide site, you signify your assent to the OzCarGuide On-line Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our sites. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

## PLEASE READ THIS DISCLAIMER CAREFULLY

Information on this Internet site should not be regarded as a substitute for professional legal, financial advice.

OzCarGuide and its related entities responsible for maintaining this Internet site and its directors, officers and agents believe that all information contained within this Internet web site is correct. However, no warranty is made as to the accuracy or reliability of the information contained herein and ozcarguide.com disclaims all liability and responsibility for any direct or indirect loss or damage which may be suffered by any recipient through relying on anything contained in or omitted from the Internet site at www.ozcarguide.com

Copyright 2007 – OzCarGuide.com All Rights Reserved. The text, images, graphics, sound files, animation files, video files and their arrangement on ozcarguide.com are all subject to copyright and other intellectual property protection. These objects many not be copied for commercial use or distribution, nor may these objects be modified or posted to other sites. Some of ozcarguide.com also contain images that are subject to copyright rights or their providers. © ozcarguide.com.
